http://www.paperindex.com/policies/privacy-policy

Contact Buyers
Privacy Policy PaperIndex respects your online time and privacy and your confidentiality is important to us.
PaperIndex members are assured that none of the information submitted to PaperIndex will ever be sold or redistributed without express consent.
Policy Overview
This is the Privacy Policy governing the use of PaperIndex website. By using this site, you consent to our Privacy Policy as set out below. By providing any personal information to this site, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information. You are responsible for checking this page periodically for changes and updates to the Privacy Policy. Your use of PaperIndex website following any posted changes to the Privacy Policy will be deemed an acceptance of such changes. If you do not agree with the practices explained in this policy document, do not complete the Sign Up form and contact us.
Information Collection and Use
PaperIndex is a Web-based marketplace that connects buyers and suppliers in paper and related industries. PaperIndex is the sole owner of the information collected on this website. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this policy statement. PaperIndex will not provide any personally identifying information on individual members to any third party.
Registration
To be a PaperIndex member, buyers, and suppliers must first complete the registration / sign up form. During registration, buyers and suppliers are required to provide their contact information (i.e. name, address, phone number, and email address). Any and all information provided will not be sold to third parties and is completely confidential.
Published Information
Any information disclosed to PaperIndex for publishing on its website becomes public information and is not subject to copyright any other proprietary right. If you want to retain copyright or any other proprietary right, do not submit that information on PaperIndex.
Credit Card Payment
Any credit card information that you provide through PaperIndex website is directly submitted to a third party credit card processor. PaperIndex does not maintain electronic or physical copies of your credit card information. While PaperIndex uses up-to-date technology and internal procedures to guard your payment details, there is no guarantee that such technology or procedure can eliminate all of the risks of theft, loss, or misuse. PaperIndex shall not be liable to you or any other entity or person for any damages that might arise from unauthorized use, publication, disclosure, or any other misuse of payment details, including credit card information.
Cookies
Cookies are text files that websites use to capture information about the members and visitors. PaperIndex uses cookies to recognize the information buyers and suppliers provide on our website. (For example, a registered member signs out of PaperIndex. The member returns to PaperIndex to sign into the website. The member's username already appears in the login form, and the member is only required to enter their password to login.) PaperIndex members must have cookies enabled on their browser(s). Cookie preferences are set within each browser's Internet options/preferences menu. Should PaperIndex allow advertisers on the website, some of these advertisers may use cookies. PaperIndex will have no access to or control over these cookies. You can control if and how a cookie will be accepted by configuring your browser settings. By setting your preferences in the browser, you can accept or reject cookies. If you disable cookies, you may be required to re-enter your information on our website more often and certain features of our website may not be available.
Log Files
PaperIndex logs IP addresses for system administration purposes. This information is used to diagnose server problems, monitor traffic patterns, analyze trends, administer the website, track user patterns, and identify the most popular areas of the website to deliver content most relevant to members. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information and are only used to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, except in the case of fraud.
Web Beacons
PaperIndex Web pages may contain an electronic file called a web beacon, which allows a website to count its users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies. In general, any file served as part of a web page, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon. PaperIndex may use web beacons in HTML-formatted email messages or e-newsletters (messages that include graphics) to determine which email messages were opened and to note whether a message was acted upon. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie, which identifies the referring source, pages viewed and the time of access. Web beacons are not used to access your personal information on PaperIndex. PaperIndex may also include web beacons from advertisers on its web pages to provide the advertisers auditing and research reports.
Security
PaperIndex suggests that you protect your password. PaperIndex will never ask your password over phone or in an e-mail. You should not disclose your password to anyone including PaperIndex Customer Care representatives. If you use a public computer, you should not save your sign in information (i.e. username and password) on the computer. Also, do not forget to sign out of your account and close the browser window when you are done. Please note, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. While PaperIndex takes every precaution to protect registered member information, no website or company, including PaperIndex, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.
Sharing
Should PaperIndex share aggregated demographic information with partners, customers, and/or advertisers, or potential users such information will not be linked to personal information that identifies individual members.
Links
PaperIndex contains links to other websites and is not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites. PaperIndex encourages its members to read the privacy policies of all websites linked to PaperIndex website. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by PaperIndex.
Mandatory Communications
PaperIndex sends all newly registered members a welcome email to verify their email addresses. We also send emails when a company is registered in our directory or when we deny the listing of a company, its RFQ and product listings. etc. At times, PaperIndex sends service announcements to its registered users and members. Members cannot unsubscribe from service announcements that discuss upcoming changes affecting their PaperIndex accounts. In addition, we may communicate with members via personal emails or phone calls to provide requested services.
Optional Communications
Members may receive monthly e-newsletters containing information on PaperIndex services and announcements. Occasionally, members receive e-postcards that highlight special PaperIndex announcements and features. Registered members can opt-out of the above-listed communications.
Choice / Opt-out
Upon registration, members can opt-out of our newsletters and/or service emails. At any time, members can modify their PaperIndex email (service announcement) preferences by updating their account information in the Dashboard area of their account.
Disclosure of Information
We reserve the right to disclose your information to authorities when we have reasons to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify and bring legal action against anyone involved in illegal activities or causing injury to or losses to PaperIndex, its users, customers, and partners. We also reserve the right to disclose your information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when such disclosure is required by law, regulation, or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority. If we come to know that a user is in breach of the terms of User Agreement or any other agreement with us, we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose the user’s information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further losses to PaperIndex and/or related parties. We also reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement for investigation or prosecution.
Minors
PaperIndex website is not intended for use by persons under the age of thirteen. Individuals who are under the age of thirteen are prohibited from submitting to PaperIndex or posting to the website any personally identifiable information about themselves.
Correction / Updating Personal Information
Members may update their information listed in the Dashboard section. In addition, members who desire to opt-out of our service may deactivate their accounts at any time by updating their account settings in the Dashboard area of their account.
Notification of Changes
PaperIndex reserves the right to change this policy as required. If we alter our Privacy Policy, we will send email notification to all members. If we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from what was stated at the time of user registration, we will notify members via email. At that time, members can choose whether or not PaperIndex may use their information in a different manner. It is also possible that PaperIndex, its subsidiaries or joint ventures, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such an event occur, you should expect that PaperIndex would share some or all of your information to continue to provide the services. Notice of any such event will be posted on the PaperIndex website. Please note that the new entity may not follow the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy. Comments and feedback about PaperIndex Privacy Policy are welcome. Please contact us with your feedback by filling the contact form or creating a support ticket.
PRINT THIS PAGE
Continue browsing PaperIndex
Top Supplier Categories
A4 Copy Paper, US Letter, Legal Size Copier Paper (Laser / Inkjet) / A3, A2, A1, A0 Photocopy Paper
Bag Papers
Bags (Bulk Packaging Sacks)
Boxes, Corrugated
Business Forms / Stationery
Carbonless Copy Paper (CCP / NCR Paper)
(CB / CF / CFB)
Computer Printout Papers
Copy / Copier Paper Rolls (Laser / Inkjet)
Duplex Board / Double Layer Board (Coated: LWC, HWC / Uncoated) (Grey Back / White Back / Kraft Back)
Facial Tissue
Facial Tissue Paper (Parent / Jumbo Rolls)
Fluting Paper / Corrugating Medium Paper (Recycled / Semi-Chemical)
Food Containers
Hardwood Pulp (Bleached) (BHKP / NBHKP)
Kraft Paper (Virgin / Recycled) (Bleached / Unbleached or Brown)
Linerboard (Recycled) / Testliner
Napkin Paper (Parent / Jumbo Rolls)
Newsprint (Standard / Speciality / Improved)
Notebooks
OCC (Old Corrugated Containers)
OCC 11 (98/2, 95/5, 90/10, 80/20) (Grade 11 Old Corrugated Containers) Waste Paper
OINP 9 (OI / OIN / Grade 9 Over Issued Newspaper / Unsold Newspaper) Waste Paper
ONP 8 (Old Newspaper Grade 8) Waste Paper
Offset Paper / Woodfree Offset Printing Paper
Old Corrugated Containers (OCC)
Old Newspaper / Newsprint (ONP)
Packaging Paper Stocklots / Joblots
Paper Cups
Paper Napkins (Plain / Embossed / Colored / White / Printed / Z Fold)
Waste Paper)
Specialty Paper Stocklots / Joblots
Thermal / Fax Paper Rolls
Tissue Paper Stocklots / Joblots
Tissues
Toilet Tissue Paper (Parent / Jumbo Rolls)
Toilet Tissue Paper Rolls
Woodfree Paper / Freesheet Paper
Wrapping Papers
Top Product Categories
A4 Copy Paper, US Letter, Legal Size Copier Paper (Laser / Inkjet) / A3, A2, A1, A0 Photocopy Paper
Bag Making Machines
Bag Papers
Boxes, Set-up (Rigid)
Carbonless Copy Paper (CCP / NCR Paper) (CB / CF / CFB)
Coated Fine Papers
Coating Machines
Copy / Copier Paper Rolls (Laser / Inkjet)
Duplex Board / Double Layer Board (Coated: LWC, HWC / Uncoated) (Grey Back / White Back / Kraft Back)
Facial Tissue (Jumbo / Parent Rolls)
Fluting Paper / Corrugating Medium Paper
Inkjet Paper
Kraft Paper (Virgin / Recycled) (Bleached / Unbleached or Brown)
Newsprint (Standard / Improved / Specialty)
Notebooks
Offset Paper / Woodfree Offset Printing Paper
Paper Bags (Flat)
Paper Machine (Complete)
Paper Towels (Rolls)
Toilet Tissue (Jumbo / Parent Rolls)
Toilet Tissue (Rolls and Sheets)
Woodfree Paper / Freesheet Paper
Wrapping Papers
Xerocopy / Xerographic Paper
Top RFQ Categories
A4 Copy Paper, US Letter, Legal Size Copier Paper (Laser / Inkjet) / A3, A2, A1, A0 Photocopy Paper
Bag Making Machines
Bag Papers
Bond Paper
Carbonless Copy Paper (CCP / NCR Paper) (CB / CF / CFB)
Cardboard
Coated Fine Papers
Copy / Copier Paper Rolls (Laser / Inkjet)
Duplex Board / Double Layer Board (Coated: LWC, HWC / Uncoated) (Grey Back / White Back / Kraft Back)
Facial Tissue (Jumbo / Parent Rolls)
Fluting Paper / Corrugating Medium Paper
Greaseproof Paper
Kraft Paper (Virgin / Recycled) (Bleached / Unbleached or Brown)
Newsprint (Standard / Improved / Specialty)
Paper Towels (Rolls)
Paperboard Stocklots / Joblots
Printing & Writing Paper Stocklots / Joblots
SBS (Solid Bleached Sulphate Board) / SBB (Solid Bleached Board) (Coated: AZ, GZ / Uncoated: UZ)
Specialty Paper Stocklots / Joblots
Thermal / Fax Paper Rolls
Tissue Paper Stocklots / Joblots
Toilet Tissue (Jumbo / Parent Rolls)
Toilet Tissue (Rolls and Sheets)
© 2006 - 2020 PaperIndex.com. All rights reserved.
